Christopher Snitchler

(248)210-0994 | chris@n30.us | Holly, MI 48442

SUMMARY

Experienced Integrated Systems Administrator with a focus on Digital Out of Home Entertainment. Drawing from a solid technical foundation and a genuine drive for crafting immersive experiences, with a commitment to guaranteeing smooth operations and fine-tuned performance of integrated systems.

Collaborated closely with the Vice President of Games & Entertainment to develop and execute a strategic vision that generated \$100 million in additional revenue over the life of the Amusements Department.

EXPERIENCE

Integrated Systems Administrator, Lucky Strike Entertainment LLC, 2021 - Current Encino, CA (Remote)

Lucky Strike is a premier experiential entertainment brand. With 14 nationwide locations, 7 featuring industry-leading arcades.

- Directed the complete management of the Customer Data Environment (CDE) while concurrently leading Point of Sale operations, resulting in improved data accuracy, enhanced customer insights, and a 15% increase in sales revenue.
- Spearheaded the development and implementation of rigorous disaster recovery strategies, resulting in a 30% increase in system uptime, and a 60% reduction in data recovery time.
- Led the successful virtualization of the MICROS system, aligning with disaster recovery policy; increased system reliability by 60% and minimized potential revenue loss during downtime.
- Engineered a streamlined and integrated systems environment by creating, enhancing, and regularly maintaining system automation scripts, yielding a 30% increase in operational efficiency.
- Expanded the implementation of ConnectWise Automate, automating patch management tasks and decreasing patch deployment time by 60%, consequently enhancing system stability and security.
- Orchestrated the implementation of monitoring and alert systems across the Customer Data Environment (CDE), resulting in a 30% reduction in overall system downtime and enabling timely resolution of critical issues for enhanced operational efficiency.
- Launched a seamless hardware refresh project, migrating all on-premise CDE systems to state-of-the-art infrastructure; reducing maintenance costs by 40%.
- Championed the smooth migration of FreedomPay's payment system from FPPOS to FCCD, resulting in a 40% reduction in transaction processing errors and a 20% increase in customer satisfaction ratings.

Point of Sale Manager, Lucky Strike Entertainment LLC, 2017 - 2021 Sherman Oaks, CA (Remote)

- Implemented and maintained the MICROS RES 3700 systems in all 19 venues nationwide, resulting in a significant contribution of approximately \$115 million in total annual revenue.
- Achieved an outstanding 99% in-house resolution rate for MICROS support by expertly configuring and optimizing venue setups, ensuring uninterrupted service and exceptional customer experience.
- Programmed and customized SIM scripts, optimizing property-level configurations for seamless revenue center and service type setups; reducing manual setup time by 50%.
- Led the staging, configuration, deployment, patching, and system administration of all MICROS servers and terminals, ensuring consistent performance across venues.

Christopher Snitchler

(248)210-0994 | chris@n30.us | Holly, MI 48442

- Delivered comprehensive hardware and software support for 15+ venues, swiftly troubleshooting and resolving technical issues, resulting in a reduction in downtime and ensuring seamless operations.
- Designed equipment site plans for new venues, overseeing hardware deployment and system configuration/programming.
- Addressed level 1 support requests for companies' software products, including Salesforce, Tripleseat, MyMicros, custom event booking, and event deposit payment platforms.
- Pioneered the design and implementation of a comprehensive BI reporting and analytics platform, equipping stakeholders with actionable insights; optimized marketing spend by 15% and achieved a 30% improvement in operational efficiency.
- Maintained, programmed, and repaired aging A/V systems in all venues before individual venue upgrades, ensuring uninterrupted entertainment experiences.
- Served as a crucial liaison between the company and primary A/V vendor, facilitating effective communication and timely solutions.

Game Room Manager, Revel and Roll, 2016 - 2017 Ann Arbor, MI

Games & Redemption Manager, Lucky Strike / FTW, 2015 - 2016 Chicago, IL

Technical Manager, Lucky Strike Entertainment LLC, 2008 - 2015 Novi, MI

EDUCATION AND CERTIFICATIONS

- Certified Level 1 Duo Administrator, Duo Security 2023
- Automate Administrator, ConnectWise 2023
- Automate Service Technician, ConnectWise 2023
- A/V Technologist, AVIXA 2020
- Google IT Support Professional, Google 2020

SKILLS

- Server and Systems Administration
- Troubleshooting and Maintenance
- Automation
- Network Security
- Network Administration
- Project Management

- Disaster Planning and Recovery
- Help Desk Support
- IT Infrastructure Management
- IT Hardware Support
- CI/CD Pipelines

BOARD MEMBERSHIP

Board Member, American Amusement Manufacturers Charitable Foundation, 2023 - Current

The American Amusement Machine Charitable Foundation (AAMCF) was organized with the purpose of raising and distributing funds to organizations that support children. We sponsor fundraising events throughout the year benefiting children's charities. To date, the AAMCF has donated over \$2,000,000 to children's charities across the globe.